# H.R. Johnson

Community-Driven in Kalamazoo, Michigan 360-951-0354

find.serendipity@gmail.com & amazonxprincezz@yahoo.com github.com/Find-Serendipity & linkedin.com/in/findserendipity

#### Summary

Experienced professional with 10+ years in customer service and community management. Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, with a commitment to excellence and attention to detail. Adherent to high standards while working to understand, meet, and exceed guest expectations.

#### Skills

Languages || French (Intermediate), JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, LaTeX, PHP

Tools and Technologies || HTML, CSS, React.js, Laravel, REST, Git, Express.js, Node.js, Next.js, PostgreSQL, JSON, Prisma, Jest, JWT, bcrypt, Jira, HubSpot CRM, Apps Scripts, Miro, Figma, Canva, Hootsuite, Zendesk, GitHub, VS Code, WSL, Docker, Linux, Kanban, Agile, A/B Testing

#### Experience

## Air Zoo Museum, Kalamazoo, MI || Guest Experience Ambassador

Aug 24 – Current

- Guided guests through museum experience while operating from a stationary assignment.
- Engaged with guests, provide information about artifacts at the museum, and correctly answer guest questions.
- Helped manage flow of crowds, efficiently helping guests with needs and directing as needed.
- Ensured guest safety in various situations with various crowd sizes.

#### Communitrix, Remote | Founder

Sep 2023 – Current

- Obtained and maintained small but strong client base
- Drafted and implemented custom community plans for clients
- Maintained client codebases and updated websites with modern security
- Created standard and milestone-based contracts for clients

#### Community.co, Remote | Community Manager

July 2019 - June 2023

- Designed and developed Apps Scripts for engagement and retention projects.
- Used ChatGPT to draft and refine content, automated responses, and enhance customer experience.
- Managed VIP, CEO, and Influencer publishing and community events.
- Increased community activity from 2% to 7% through strategic initiatives.
- Trained team members in community tactics and reporting.

### Internet Brands, Remote | Community Manager

July 2013 - July 2019

- Managed cross-functional teams in community forums and customer support.
- Assisted with project management, product development and UX design.
- Increased customer satisfaction from 61% to 96%.
- Handled escalated customer support issues and abuse reports.

## Education

## Fullstack Academy, Remote $\parallel$ Junior Developer

Feb 2024 - June 2024

- Top-ranking graduate of the online full-time full-stack web development bootcamp.
- Learned advanced web engineering through hands-on projects and coursework.
- Acted as project manager, implementing tickets, pull requests, and continuous integration testing using GitHub.

## University of Washington, Seattle | Bachelor of Arts in Anthropology

2011

- Top-ranking graduate, Summa cum laude
- Focused on Archaeology, Anthropology, Oceanography, Geology